vaporesso.com 2017-06-10

# Privacy Policy | Vaporesso

This privacy policy sets out how uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

We use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages on our Websites, or register for the Subscription Service, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the HubSpot Subscription Service or Websites you visit. HubSpot keeps track of the Websites and pages you visit within HubSpot, in order to determine what portion of the HubSpot Website or Subscription Service is the most popular or most used. This data is used to deliver customized content and promotions within the HubSpot Website and Subscription Service to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

  **Cookie Name  ** |   **Domain**   |   **Vendor**   |   **Purpose**   | Category  
---|---|---|---|---  
 AWSELB  |  app.hubspot.com  |  Amazon  |  AWS Elastic Load Balancer  | Performance  
 __utma  |  hubspot.com  |  Google  |  Google Analytics  | Targeting  
 __utmb  |  hubspot.com  |  Google  |  Google Analytics  | Targeting  
 __utmc  |  hubspot.com  |  Google  |  Google Analytics  | Targeting  
 __utmz  |  hubspot.com  |  Google  |  Google Analytics  | Targeting  
 _gauges_unique_hour  |  hubspot.com  |  Gauges  |  Gauges Analytics  | Performance  
 _gauges_unique_day  |  hubspot.com  |  Gauges  |  Gauges Analytics  | Performance  
 _gauges_unique_month  |  hubspot.com  |  Gauges  |  Gauges Analytics  | Performance  
 _gauges_unique_year  |  hubspot.com  |  Gauges  |  Gauges Analytics  | Performance  
 _gauges_unique  |  hubspot.com  |  Gauges  |  Gauges Analytics  | Performance  
 apex__product  |  hubspot.com  |  SalesForce  |  SalesForce Analytics  | Strictly Necessary  
 __hstc  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Analytics  | Targeting  
 __hssrc  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Analytics  | Targeting  
 __hssc  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Analytics  | Targeting  
 hsfirstvisit  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Analytics  | Targeting  
 hsPagesViewedThisSession  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Analytics  | Strictly Necessary  
 hubspotutk  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Analytics  | Strictly Necessary  
 hubspot.hub.id  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Authentication  | Strictly Necessary  
 hubspotauth  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Authentication  | Strictly Necessary  
 hubspotauthcms  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Authentication  | Strictly Necessary  
 hubspotauthremember  |  hubspot.com  |  HubSpot  |  HubSpot Authentication  | Functionality  
_hs_opt_out | hubspot.com | HubSpot | Opt out of HubSpot tracking | Targeting  
hubspotutktzo | academy.hubspot.com  | HubSpot | Time Zone Offset | Functionality  
__hluid | hubspot.com  | HubSpot | In-app usage tracking | Targeting  
mp_id_mixpanel | hubspot.com  | Mixpanel | In-app usage tracking | Targeting
